[{"answer": "Well, Mr. my friend, I've got a really good idea for a hat. It combines the spirit of old that place with a little big city panache. I like to call it the Urban Sombrero", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Are you okay, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, you're your own boss now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Go ahead", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hi, my friend. my friend, you remember my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend, I did. It didn't work out, though, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "See ya", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend, you can't leave", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Isn't it that place now", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You guys both have class at the same time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What do you mean you're in the same class", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Wink", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh. I know they have some monies", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Not", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "This is what you used to build me up? This is where you got all that stupid katra stuff", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Search... for my friend?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What is that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, nobody sees the... cover.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You! This is all your fault! You told me I could run the company", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, I'll see ya...", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Okay, let's see. The beachhouse. 48 acres... ooh. that place. That should fetch a fair price", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Foundation.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Of course, it would have been yours", "qsentId": 28}]